popcornhour.com 2014-06-25

# Cloud Media - Privacy Policy

**What is your privacy policy?**

At Cloud Media, we believe that, as our online visitor, you have the right to know our practices regarding the information we collect when you visit our websites, and what type of information is collected. The guidelines contained herein apply to your visits to all websites operated by Cloud Media but does not include any redirect URLs that link the users to another internet domain. Other websites which are linked to/from Cloud Media websites and its affiliates may have different policies; therefore, please review the privacy policy notices on those websites for details.

**What Information is collected (Personal, “Cookies”)?**

Cloud Media only collects personal information on a voluntary basis. If an online visitor submits information to Cloud Media, it will usually take the form of either: (1) the purchase of goods through our online stores, (2) product or account registration, or registration for online participation, (3) message boards or forum, (4) warranty registration, (5) content registration, (6) a consumer complaint, (7) survey, (8) customer service or technical support, and/or (9) a newsletter. Personal information collected may include your name, home address, phone number, and/or e-mail address. We do not require this information to gain access to our sites, however you will not be able to utilize certain products, services, or features that require registration or receive materials such as newsletter unless such information is provided.

Visitors purchasing products will be required to provide additional information such as a valid credit card number, expiration date, and shipping and billing address via PayPal Account.

Please note that, depending on the Cloud Media site that you are visiting, many of the activities listed above may not be available and, as such, personal information may not be collected.

For each visitor who visits any of Cloud Media's websites and its affiliates, Cloud Media's web server automatically recognizes and stores information, such as the visitor's IP address/domain name combination and any referring websites. We use this information to understand visitor traffic patterns through our websites for purposes such as enhancing their usability. Your computer provides this information automatically each time you log on, unless you have activated blocking technology available in some browsers.

When you visit Cloud Media websites or advertisements appearing thereon, or use one or more of the Cloud Media's website services, we may use an industry-wide technology called “cookies” which stores certain information on your computer and which allows us to customize your experience to better match your interests and preferences, or to simply facilitate your signing in to use the services. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies, we may not be able to restore any preferences or customization settings you previously specified, and our ability to personalize your online experience would be limited. Please refer to your browser’s instructions or “help” screen to learn more about these functions.

Additionally, Cloud Media or third parties on its behalf may collect anonymous information from visits to our sites through the use of “Web Beacons”. Web Beacons are electronic Web Page images that enable us to record anonymous data about visits to our website. This anonymous information is sometimes known as “clickstream data”. We may use this data to analyse trends and statistics to improve your online experience, or customer service. No personal data is collected through the use of Web Beacons on our websites.

**How do we use your personal information?**

The personal information you provide Cloud Media will allow us to fulfil your product or service order; alert you of new products or services, features, or enhancements; handle/route your customer service or technical support questions or issues; and/or notify you promotions and offers. Cloud Media will not reveal your personal information to other companies or organizations.

Lastly, we may use your personal information for internal marketing, profiling, or demographic purposes, so we can adapt our products and services to better suit your needs. We do this to better understand and serve our customers.

**What type of communication may I receive?**

_Special Offers and updates_

We will occasionally send you information on products, services and special deals and promotions. Out of respect of your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communication. Please see the “What choices do I have” section below.

What choices do I have regarding the collection, use, and distribution of my personal information?

Cloud Media allows you to control the way that we use personal identifying information that we might obtain. At the time you provide personal information, Cloud Media may give you the option of declining any future offers or information about new products, promotions or services. In addition, many of the “mailings” that Cloud Media may send you, such as newsletters, have the procedures within them to cancel the receipt of any future mailings. Lastly you may be given the opportunity to “opt-out”.

**How secure is my personal information?**

Cloud Media has taken steps to assure that all information collected will remain secure and in its original form, i.e. free from any alteration. As such, access to all personal information is strictly controlled.

**Security**

While Cloud Media cannot guarantee that unauthorized access by external parties will never occur, rest assured that Cloud Media takes great care in maintaining the security of your personal information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through the use of appropriate technologies and internal procedures.

**Notice to/ Regarding Children under the Age of 13**

If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information (for example, your last name, home address or e-mail address) on this site without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. If Cloud Media learns that you are under 13 years of age, Cloud Media will not maintain or use any personally identifiable information about you without the verifiable consent of your parent or guardian, except as allowed by law. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the sites without that certifiable consent.

Cloud Media believes that children using the Internet require special protecting, and we urge parents or guardians to explain Internet safety to their children. Parents are urged to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on Cloud Media websites (including and not limited to www.cloudmedia.com) and the Internet in general. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers to help create a safer environment for children.

**Consent to Processing**

By providing any personal information to Cloud Media, all users internationally fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in Malaysia.

**Policy Governs Use, Changes of Privacy Policy**

Our privacy policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce you rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.
